Departments 

 [ Bookmark us!](javascript:addBookmark('https://www.asseenontvlive.com','As Seen On TV');) [Redeem Gift Card](https://www.asseenontvlive.com/redeem/) [Help](https://www.asseenontvlive.com/help/)

**The As Seen On TV App is here!**  

**The As Seen On TV App is here!**  

### Privacy Policy

As Seen On TV believes that the establishment of trust and privacy is instrumental to the continued growth of the Internet. We've created this privacy statement to demonstrate our corporate commitment to individual privacy. The policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services. By using the As Seen On TV website, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth below.

**Collection of Personal Information**

As Seen On TV collects personal information including, without limitations, name, address, e-mail address, telephone, demographic data and member identification number from its members and users. We may collect such personal information as part of the checkout process for customers, or when visitors submit comments or other correspondence to us through this website or otherwise. Additionally, As Seen On TV may collect personal information through its web site by using cookies, social media, or other methods of monitoring web usage. We do not market, sell, or trade this information to any outside companies, but collected information may be shared with our business partners and marketplace vendors; for example, your address is shared with vendors for the purpose of delivering your order. We do not share e-mail addresses or payment information with Vendors or any other third parties.

We may, at times, use the demographic information as a marketing or promotional tool. When we do that, we will make sure it remains entirely anonymous.

**Cookies**

As Seen On TV uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart items. The type of cookies we use are stored both on our server and on your computer, to allow you to retain items you've added to your cart should you navigate away from the site and return later.

**Security**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (a valid email address), unique identifiers (a password), financial information (credit card number), and demographic information (such as a zip code). When this type of information is collected it travels through the Internet in encrypted form. Our entire site is run using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which provides strong cryptography, to transfer all of the personal information to us. Financial and login information (password) are transmitted in accordance with our [Safe Shopping Policy](https://www.asseenontvlive.com/policies/safe-shopping/) and are never shared with third parties.

* * *

Get to Know Us

Get Help

* * *

Copyright © 2024 [As Seen On TV](https://www.asseenontvlive.com/), Inc.

Copyright © 2024 [As Seen On TV](https://www.asseenontvlive.com/), Inc.

Brand logos ® © their respective trademark holders. Not all products have appeared on television.
